[Music]
Heat.
You don't call me baby,
you call me your name.
But I keep on hoping nothing has
changed.
Yeah.
We keep on touching,
but we don't feel
it. Feels like you're letting your hands
are the wheel.
[Music]
What if I just hold on for a while?
Baby, there's no clock quite like
denial. Oh my.
If this is a goodbye,
don't leave me loving you.
Whatever you do,
don't leave me loving you. Tiptoe out in
the morning. I need a warning. If you
don't feel it, too.
Whatever you do,
the way we me.
[Music]
The sun is setting
in purple and blue.
It's no getting closer to you.
Yeah.
Waking up strangers
and California game.
Reaching out for you to bring you to me.
Yeah.
What if I just hold on for a while?
Baby, there's no clock quite like
denial. Oh my.
If this is a goodbye,
don't leave me loving you.
Whatever you do,
don't leave me
out in the morning.
If you don't feel
whatever you do
on this morning,
[Music]
whatever you do,
Heat. Heat.
[Music]
me loving you.
Whatever you do,
don't leave me loving you. If you tiptoe
out in the morning, I need a warning.
Leave me loving you.
[Music]
You don't call me baby,
you call me my name.
But I keep on hoping nothing has
changed.
Yeah,
we keep on touching.
[Music]
But we don't feel
it. Feels like you're letting your hands
up the wheel.
But I just hold for a while. Baby,
there's no clock like tonight. Oh,
if this isn't good,
don't leave me loving you.
Whatever you do,
don't leave me
out in the morning. be one if you don't
feel it too.
Whatever you do,
[Music]
Leave me loving you. For the music
video, I came up uh with a treatment
that follows my uh previous release. Uh
pretty please. Uh still staying in the
time zone of uh '90s Hong Kong Chinese
movie style. Yeah, the way I decided to
shoot the video, uh, it's more towards,
uh, movie structure this time rather
than like the musical and coro
performances, uh, like I always do.
What if I just hold on for a while?
Baby, there's no clock quite like
denial. Oh my
goodbye.
The story line of Leave Me Loving You
music video. Well, it's another love
story. Uh I'm playing a role of a
dishwasher in a restaurant and I fell in
love with this girl since the day she
came in. Everything about this love
story only happened in my mind. Uh it's
my imagination and never happened. Uh
she doesn't know me. And
lastly, she got married.
Very simple story, but very interesting
to shoot it in a different style this
time.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
Oh,
the way we love you.